<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lewis A. Jones</title>
    <link>https://lewisajones.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lewis A. Jones</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lewisajones.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://lewisajones.com/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewisajones.com/experience/</guid>
      <description>Lewis A. Jones Postdoctoral Research Fellow Vigo, Spain LewisAlan.Jones@uvigo.es Education  PhD in Earth Sciences (2016–2020) Imperial College London, London, UK Research advisors: Dr Philip D. Mannion &amp;amp; Prof. Peter A. Allison Thesis title: On the detectability of the latitudinal biodiversity gradient in deep time
MPhysGeog in Physical Geography (2011–2015) University of Hull, Hull, UK Research advisor: Prof. David P.G. Bond Thesis title: The End-Triassic mass extinction. An investigation of the British Geological Record: testing for the role of volcanism and ocean anoxia CMI (Level 5) in Management and Leadership (2012–2015) Leeds University Officer Training Corps, Leeds, UK</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://lewisajones.com/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewisajones.com/research/</guid>
      <description>  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://lewisajones.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewisajones.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Lewis A. Jones, PhD
Postdoctoral Research Fellow
Mapas Lab, Centro de Investigación Mariña, Universidade de Vigo LewisAlan.Jones@uvigo.es
I am a computational palaeobiologist investigating the drivers of biodiversity patterns across a range of temporal and spatial scales. My research primarily focuses on the co-evolution of life and the environment, and evaluating the influence of data incompleteness on our perceptions of the geological past. To do so, I integrate a range of interdisciplinary tools and sources of information, such as ecological niche modelling, fossil occurrence data, and palaeoclimatic models to estimate species’ distributions in deep time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://lewisajones.com/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewisajones.com/gallery/</guid>
      <description>  Now and then, I take photographs. Here are some shots I have collected over the years.
White Sands, USA.
Wolf Creek, USA.
Arolla, Switzerland.
Allgäu, Germany.
Richmond Park, UK.
Hull, UK.
Hull, UK.
Hull, UK.
Street food market, Harbin, China.
Shenyang, China.
Harbin, China. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://lewisajones.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewisajones.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>Peer-reviewed publications Lewis A. Jones, Philip D. Mannion, Alexander Farnsworth, Fran Bragg, Daniel J. Lunt (2022). Climatic and tectonic drivers shaped the tropical distribution of coral reefs. Nature Communications. 13 (3120), 1–10. View graphical abstract.
 Lewis A. Jones and Kilian Eichenseer (2022). Uneven spatial sampling distorts reconstructions of Phanerozoic seawater temperature. Geology 50 (2), 238–242. View graphical abstract.
 Lewis A. Jones, Christopher D. Dean, Philip D. Mannion, Alexander Farnsworth, Peter A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Packages</title>
      <link>https://lewisajones.com/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewisajones.com/software/</guid>
      <description>palaeoverse The palaeoverse R package is a community-driven toolkit to support the preparation and exploration of palaeobiological data. The package provides a suite of auxiliary functions, is open-source, and freely available from the CRAN. palaeoverse has three core principles: (1) streamline data preparation and exploration; (2) enhance code readability; and (3) improve reproducibility of results. It is my hope that over time, palaeoverse will be adopted and developed by the community, with contributors and users from across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uneven spatial sampling and reconstructing past global temperatures</title>
      <link>https://lewisajones.com/posts/2021/11/uneven-spatial-sampling-and-reconstructing-past-global-temperatures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewisajones.com/posts/2021/11/uneven-spatial-sampling-and-reconstructing-past-global-temperatures/</guid>
      <description>Accounting for the spatial nature of proxy records is crucial to improving reconstructions of past global temperature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Latitudinal Biodiversity Gradient</title>
      <link>https://lewisajones.com/posts/2021/04/the-latitudinal-biodiversity-gradient/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lewisajones.com/posts/2021/04/the-latitudinal-biodiversity-gradient/</guid>
      <description>One of the most prominent macroecological patterns on Earth today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
